<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Finite musings]]></title>
  <link href="http://finitud.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://finitud.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2014-05-30T20:24:22+01:00</updated>
  <id>http://finitud.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[wyan]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Should I Stay or Should I Go]]></title>
    <link href="http://finitud.github.io/blog/2014/05/30/should-i-stay-or-should-i-go/"/>
    <updated>2014-05-30T18:32:17+01:00</updated>
    <id>http://finitud.github.io/blog/2014/05/30/should-i-stay-or-should-i-go</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I am considering moving again. The flat I moved into three months ago is nice enough
for one, but it seems that lacking a living room puts people off renting the room,
and things being as they are I can’t afford the whole thing myself.</p>

<p>So what am I thinking about?</p>

<!-- //more -->

<ul>
  <li>It would be cool to have a place with plenty of space (as I have now)</li>
  <li>Some outdoors (garden, terrace…) and some privacy</li>
  <li>Maybe a cheaper city? Cheaper country?</li>
</ul>

<p>The current place has enough space for me, at least for now. And that’s counting
with the fact that the room is empty, and I want to throw away / sell / give away
some of the stuff that’s still in boxes. The room should be enough for someone
in a similar situation—someone not requiring a living room or massive amounts
of space, who likes to take it easy and quiet in their room or be out often.
The kitchen isn’t too big, but it’s not the smallest I’ve had, either. It’s got
pretty much anything you may want in a kitchen, except for a dining table (and
a folding one would fit). The hall/entrance/corridor is enormous, there’s definitely
space for a chilling area there, if needed.</p>

<p>Of course, there are downsides. It’s directly on the street, at street level, so
there isn’t much privacy unless the curtains are closed, and no place where to
make a nice permanent outdoors area. It’s massively overpriced—I feel like I
had to look for a flat at the peak of a craze, and nobody looking for a room seems
to be willing to pay so much. So the question of whether furnishing the room would
help stays in my mind (even though I’m being explicit in the ad that I will do so
if needed), but also the fear that I’ll just be buying more furniture that I’ll have
to put away in a few months time when I can’t pay for this flat anymore.</p>

<p>I’m still not sure what I’m doing in London. I seem to be unable to find like minded
people, still have no friends after three and a half years here, and the house market
seems to expect me to keep running full speed forever and taking away any money I can
ever make. There is no imaginable chance of being able to stay here unless it’s
by sticking full speed to the rat race. The city is ugly and unfriendly, chaotic,
cheap quality and expensive price, a speculator’s dream. But no place for slow living.</p>

<p>I miss studying. I miss the academic freedom and being able to think about things.
I don’t know how to recover these in the most expensive city in several thousand miles.</p>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
